The rest of the killers are camped inside a ring of metal.
Blood spilled calls for blood spilled.
If the ground is cursed and let our vengeance sanctify it, you bless.
Feel.
Please.
War Chief.
Break the taboo.
Definitely.
It is a cursed place.
But
the royal secret blessing can protect us.
I'll send scouts ahead.
Our force will assemble at the cliff above ran echoes and launch our attack from there.
Devil's grief.
Foreboding sight, huh?
Don't you ever wonder what it used to look like back when the old ones left?
Here?
Here.
Not like other Nora.
That's what they tell me.
War Chief.
Our scouts found enemy camps in the ruins guarding the approach to the ring of metal.
Then we should hit those camps first.
Make sure they stay quiet.
Agreed.
Wipe out the camps on our enemies in the ring of metal.
Won't see us coming.
I'll take out the alarms, will send braves to each camp to lie in Wait, which you start.
Don't help finish
Brave.
It is time.
Time to fight.
Time to kill.
Maybe time to die.
We will regroup there at the base of the tallest tower, then to the ring off metal and vengeance.
Today we break taboo to honour our dead and punish our enemies.
Blood spoons, blood spilled.
Mother, forgive our trespasses.
Can't have not Basie lay her raft solely upon me.
Now to battle.
You're taking this pretty well.
The trespassing on tainted lands thing.
I mean, you think so?
I feel like that.
Silly cards.
A priest at the blessing quaking under his hood
that night.
Already feels like a lifetime ago.
Yeah, we weren't really close of all that.
I
always competing for our mother's respect, I guess.
Well,
you have mine if it makes any difference.
Thanks.
It does.
But this battle.
I'm not doing this for respect.
Yours or my mother's.
I'm doing it for Bala.
I know.
She would have done the same for me.
Time to strike.
We'll follow your lead.
All right.
No.
Got their attention.
Wait.
Well
Oh,
look at this.
She went that a way.
Three
something up there.
Damn no more.
I got it.
Be free of all prayed today.
Victory
Hundreds over.
Yeah,
we have what we need here.
He said can't be an instrument of shadow.
Okay,
here we are,
huh?
Yeah.
No fire trucks,
right?
You got nothing better to do.
Eyes up, trying to get over on it.
No.
Yeah.
Take them
a victory for all, Mother.
No,
No!
Treat them in your sights,
Mother.
We're finished here.
You,
I'll find a use for you.
The camps have been dealt with now to the ring of metal.
Its high walls protect the enemy.
We'll have to scale the height under fire if were detected.
I have another idea.
Their base has a weakness.
Send me in alone and I'll exploit it.
If I'm successful, I'll blow a hole in those walls.
Big enough for the entire war party to charge through.
Sounds like a plan.
So long as I get to come with you.
A war chief should be grateful for two arrow so eager to spring from the bow.
Yes, well, go with a lawyer's her spear mate.
But
be vigilant.
Yes, War Chief.
I will
go now.
We wait on your signal.
You do have a plan, right?
You followed me this far, even into the ruins.
I thought you trusted me.
I do.
But how would you know that this base has a weakness?
Patients We'll know soon enough.
take my head.
Take the one on the right.
I'll take the one on the left.
What?
Two more.
You take the one on the left.
There.
See that covered shelter?
Do you see those corrupters?
Focus for that shelter is full of blaze.
Whole stockpile of it.
If I set it off, the explosion will destroy those corrupters collapsed the wall too.
A breach for the Nora to charge through.
Can hit it from here, though.
We'll need to get closer.
I'll get closer.
You head back.
Tell Sona the plan and lead them to that side of the ring.
I'll see it done.
When the wall collapses, I'll be first through the breach.
Now I have to do is make it all happen.
E can do this quietly, please.
Yeah,
Just get a place to shoot it.
Spot.
I can't get to that place fast.
Time to die!
Watch!
I'll take you down.
You
Well,
okay.
Okay.
Yeah,
like this.
Fight
all.
Mother, Look upon our victory.
A debt of blood is paid.
Remember this day, Brave Nora.
From your lips to the goddess.
His ears?
Yes.
Remember it
Ready to leave this place?
Let your spears and arrows rest in the bodies of the fallen.
They are tainted like these ruins.
It's over.
They won't be able to kill again.
The killer's this corruption.
They're all parts of the Mr Chasing Where the trail leads.
I go.
Lucky me.
Just stay out of their way for now.
Nutritious
on one of these
you
charger blaze storage canister horns.
Destroying this component disables the charge.
Attack.
Whatever the corruption is, it doesn't just affect machines.
It burns.
Flesh sickens the injured.
Do the corrupted machines have any weaknesses?
Fire seems to affect them more than ordinary machines.
A small mercy.
This's where it ends
with
how much
the flames are burning it.
Flames burn stronger than usual.
Those machines, you could see the corruption coming off them like smoke.
Time to clear them out.
Fascinating.
Looking for me?
Yeah.
Keep quiet now.
Okay.
I want to get something off my chest right now because this needs to be said to all Jesse fans and to the entire romantic fortunes fan community.
Jessica Sterling should not win romantic fortunes.
This is so obvious to anyone who actually pays attention.
I used to be like you guys last season.
I wanted Jessica to win, but is a deficit.
301 She has gone too far.
Were you people even watching?
When she rejected Louise, the sweetest human being on the planet, he stood by her through everything.
The Alaska acquisition, that time, the hairier bots malfunction mid battle.
The only reason Jessica has had any success is because Louise had her back.
He loves her, and she doesn't even care.
This is why I am throwing my support behind Vernon.
I do not take this decision lightly.
I was a Jesse fan for two whole seasons.
Jessica is the whole reason I even care about Sterling mathlete.
But as a fan, I cannot continue to support someone so heartless.
Louise, you can do better.
Yeah,
Advantage.
I wonder what show,
but because she had stormed tour Day five
Grace warms open for turtle smash the night.
I o d Here we're so the police report said it Anyway, I was 15 years old
when I woke in the hospital.
Two days later.
Her face was the first thing I saw